{
    "id": "e6eab538dc0746e2bfced31501c61525",
    "title": "Modal Auxiliary Verbs Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "She ………………… speak Italian really well.",
            "description": "We use can to talk about ability.",
            "answers": [
                "can",
                "may",
                "might"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I asked if you ………………………….. arrive in the afternoon.",
            "description": "When the verb in the main clause is in the past tense, we use a past tense in the subordinate clause. Could is the past tense of can.",
            "answers": [
                "can",
                "could",
                "might"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "She ………………………… walk when she was just nine months old.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "can",
                "could",
                "might"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "If you take rest for an hour, you ……………………… feel better.",
            "description": "All of these can be used to talk about possibility in affirmative sentences.",
            "answers": [
                "may",
                "can",
                "could",
                "might"
            ],
            "correct": 3
        },
        {
            "question": "After giving birth, a woman ……………………. suffer from depression for many months.",
            "description": "May is often used to talk about typical occurrences.",
            "answers": [
                "may",
                "can",
                "shall"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "She said that she ………………………….. go to the movies.",
            "description": "Might is the past tense of may. ",
            "answers": [
                "may",
                "can",
                "might"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "You …………………………… have lots of money, but that doesn’t mean you are better than me.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "might",
                "would",
                "should"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "When I was a child, I …………………………. watch TV whenever I wanted.",
            "description": "We use could to talk about past ability.",
            "answers": [
                "may",
                "might",
                "could"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………………… he arrive on time?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Will",
                "Would",
                "Shall"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I ………………………. be happy even if I do not win the prize.",
            "description": "Will is used to make predictions about the future. ",
            "answers": [
                "will",
                "could",
                "may"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "She …………………………… be here soon.",
            "description": "We often use should to talk about logical possibility.",
            "answers": [
                "shall",
                "should",
                "would"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I …………………………….. kill him if he reads my letters again.",
            "description": "Will is used in threats. ",
            "answers": [
                "will",
                "shall",
                "would"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        }
    ]
}